

#### Profile

Capable of progressing any project related to Software Development, especially web-development, and possess an ample of knowledge regarding programming language such as PHP, JavaScript, HTML, AJAX, NodeJS, ReactJS, REST API, Express, Mongo Web Server, etc. Having the experience of creating a web-based application in the past projects, and can be actively engaging with the team to provide the highest productivity and efficiency due to the importance of teamwork in project management.

## Employment History

Part Timer, Gadget & Tech, Kuala Lumpur

May 2019 — August 2019

- · Serve and assist customer with technical knowledge
- Constantly checkup the product for sales
- Cashier

# Frontend Developer at Webby, 2-3, Jalan Merbah 1, Bandar Puchong Jaya, 47170 Puchong, Selangor

July 2020 — November 2020

- Improvise the UI/UX based on the client's requirement and needs.
- Develop the front-end design based on the given schema.
- Fix the unintended design changes caused by other project team members.

#### Education

SPM (Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia), SMJK KEAT HWA, Kedah, Alor Setar January 2012 — December 2016

Graduate from high school with Malaysian Certificate of Education on

# Diploma, Asia Pacific University (APU), Kuala Lumpur, Kuala Lumpur

May 2017 — May 2019

the year of 2016.

Graduate from university with Diploma certificate in *Information & Communication Technology with specialism in Software* on the year of 2019, Second Upper Class with CGPA 3.1.

### Bachelor's Degree, Asia Pacific University (APU), Kuala Lumpur, Kuala Lumpur

September 2019 — December 2021

Graduate from university with Bachelor's Degree in *Computer Software Engineering* on the year of 2021, Second Upper Class with CGPA 3.33.

#### **Details**

+6 010-458 3822 joeshern123@gmail.com

#### **Skills**

PHP

AJAX

**ECMAScript** 

ReactJS

NodeJS/Express

MongoDB/Mongoose

MaterialUI

SQL

Bootstrap 4

HTML/CSS/JavaScript

C++

Java Programming

VB.Net

#### Languages

English

Chinese

Malay

#### ■ References

#### Ms. Rozita Yati Binti Masri from Asia Pacific University (APU)

rozita@apu.edu.my · +6 03-8996 1000

## Mr. Kuruvikulam Chandrasekaran Arun from Asia Pacific University (APU)

kchandran.arun@apu.edu.my · +6 03-8996 1000

#### **Y** Extra-curricular activities

# Mathematics Competition (A) at Mathematics, Accounting, and Finance (MAF) Week, Kuala Lumpur

July 2017 — July 2017

Attended a Mathematics Competition (A) in Asia Pacific University (APU), Kuala Lumpur on 14th July 2017.

## Mathematics Competition (B) at Mathematics, Accounting, and Finance (MAF) Week, Kuala Lumpur

July 2017 — July 2017

Attended a Mathematics Competition (B) in Asia Pacific University (APU), Kuala Lumpur on 14th July 2017.

### Industrial Visit in ICT at Gardenia Bakeries (KL) Sdn Bhd, Kuala Lumpur

June 2019 — June 2019

Attended an Industrial Visit in ICT to Gardenia Bakeries (KL) Sdb Bhd from Asia Pacific University (APU), Kuala Lumpur on 25th June 2018.